freshnmarine.com.sg 2014-04-19

# fresh 'n' marine aQuarium Singapore

**Privacy Policy**

**[FreshnMarine.com.sg]()** understands that you are concerned how information about yourself is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting **[www.FreshnMarine.com.sg]()** , you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. 

**1\. Commitment to Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To safeguard your privacy we provide this notice explaining:   
a. our online information practices.   
b. the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.   
c. communications from **[FreshnMarine.com.sg]()**. 

**2\. Limiting collection**

The types of personal information we collect include all the information entered in your Account pages: shipping and billing name and address, email address, birth date and phone number; and/or from a promotion quiz, e-newsletter or other marketing means organize by **[FreshnMarine.com.sg]()** via our web portal. Only the necessary personal data is collected from customers’ for business purpose. Both the amount and the type of data collected shall be limited to that which is necessary to fulfill the purpose identified. 

**[FreshnMarine.com.sg]()** does not collect your credit card information when payment is made via PayPal website.

**3\. Opt-in Communications**

When you establish an Email Sign Up, your account automatically indicates that you want to receive promotional information from **[FreshnMarine.com.sg]()** regarding news about our products, services and events. In addition, it automatically indicates that you would like to be informed about special offers, products and free samples from **[FreshnMarine.com.sg]()** partners, if any. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, you may opt-out of receiving these communications by perform your own setting through your Account Profile information, or by sending an email to **[sales@freshnmarine.com.sg](mailto:sales@freshnmarine.com.sg)** to request for removal from the mailing list. 

**4\. Communications to Serve You**

If you have elected to provide us with your contact information, e.g., by registering at the Site, emailing our Customer Service department or placing an order, we may provide you with service related announcements concerning the Site or contact you regarding your customer service requests or your order. For example, all registered users will receive a welcoming email to confirm their registration. These types of communications are necessary to serve you, respond to your concerns and to provide the high level of customer service that **[FreshnMarine.com.sg]()** offers its customers. 

**5\. No Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information for Third Party Marketing Without Your Consent**

We use the information you provide when placing an order, to process and complete that order. We would not display or make publicly available, whether through online directories, customer lists or otherwise, the personally identifiable information collected. 

In addition, we will never provide your personally identifiable information to third parties for their use in marketing their products or services to you without your consent. 

**6\. Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information**

**6.1. Fraud Protection and Compliance with Law**  
We may disclose any information, including personally identifiable information, we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. We may also exchange information, including personally identifiable information, with other companies and organisations for credit fraud protection and risk reduction. 

**6.2. Service Providers**  
We may retain other companies and individuals to perform functions consistent with our Privacy Policy on our behalf. Examples include customer support specialists, webhosting companies, fulfilment companies (e.g., companies that fill product orders or coordinate mailings), data analysis firms and email service providers. Such third parties may be provided with access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use such information for any other purpose. 

**6\. Data Security**  
At **[FreshnMarine.com.sg]()** , protecting your information is a priority. To prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and workflow procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We have developed guidelines and implemented procedures to govern the destruction of personal data that are no longer required to fulfil the identified purposes. 

**7\. Links**

This Site may contain links to or from other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. This Privacy Policy applies only to the information we collect on the Site. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of other websites you link to from the Site or otherwise visit. 

**8\. Contact Information**

We have taken great measures to ensure that your visit to the Site is an excellent one and that your privacy is constantly respected. If you have any questions, comments or concerns, please contact us by emailing to **[sales@freshnmarine.com.sg](mailto:sales@freshnmarine.com.sg)**.
